http://www.centralcoastwineservices.com/conditions-of-use

Cart
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Conditions of Use
This Website, portal.millerfamilywines.com, is operated by Miller Family Wine Brands, LLC, a California bonded winery. All references to "our", "us", "we" or "Company" refer to Miller Family Wine Brands, LLC, its subsidiaries, affiliates and/or associates, as appropriate.
The following terms and conditions, together with any documents they expressly incorporate by reference (collectively, these "Terms of Use"), govern your access to, and use of, portal.millerfamilywines.com (the "Website"), including any content, functionality and services offered on or through the Website, whether as a guest or a registered user. Please read the Terms of Use, Privacy Policy and Shipping Policy carefully before you use the Website. When accessing and using this Website, you agree to the terms and conditions that follow.
Permitted Users
This Website is intended to be used and accessed only by people who are of legal age to purchase and consume wine. If you are of legal age in your country of residence and the country from which you are accessing this Website, please continue. If you are not, please exit this Website immediately. By continuing, you affirm that you are of legal age to purchase and consume wine in your country of residence and the country from which you are accessing this Website.
Links
This Website may include links to other websites, some of them operated by third-parties. These links are provided as a convenience to you and as an additional avenue of access to the information contained therein. We have not necessarily reviewed all of the information on other sites and are not responsible for the content of any other sites or any products or services that may be offered through other sites. Inclusion of links to other sites or references to unaffiliated products should not be viewed as an endorsement of the content of linked sites. Different terms and conditions may apply to your use of any linked sites. You should review the site policies and terms of use of any linked sites.
Accuracy and Completeness
We are not responsible if information that we make available on this Website is not accurate, complete or current. The material on this Website is provided for general information only and should not be relied upon or used as the sole basis for making significant decisions without consulting primary or more accurate, more complete or more timely sources of information. Any reliance upon the material on this Website shall be at your own risk. We reserve the right to modify the contents of the Website at any time, but we have no obligation to update any information on this Website. You agree that it is your responsibility to monitor changes to the Website.
Use of Material From This Website
This Website (including all its contents) is the property of the Company or its licensors and is protected by copyright, trademark and other laws of the United States and other countries. We authorize you to browse through the Website and print and download copies of material on the Website for your personal, noncommercial use only, so long as you do not remove any copyright or other notices that appear on the material you print or download. You agree that you will not otherwise copy, display or transmit any material on the Website in any manner or medium. You also agree not to modify, sell, broadcast or distribute any material on the Website in any manner or medium, including by uploading the material or otherwise making the material available on-line.
Trademarks
This Website features logos and other trademarks and service marks that are the property of, or are licensed to the Company. The Website may also include trademarks or service marks of third parties. All of these trademarks are the property of their respective owners, and you agree not to use or display them in any manner without the prior written permission of the applicable trademark owner.
Privacy and Security
Login Required
In order to access some of the offerings on this Website, you may be asked to set up an account and password. Our account registration page requests certain personal information from you ("Registration Info"). You will have the ability to maintain and periodically update your Registration Info as you see fit. By registering, you agree that all information provided by you as Registration Info is true and accurate and that you will maintain and update this information as required in order to keep it current, complete and accurate.
Passwords & Security
If you register for an account on the Website, you agree that you are responsible for maintaining the security and confidentiality of your password, and that you are fully responsible for all activities or charges that are incurred under your account. Therefore, you must take reasonable steps to ensure that others do not gain access to your password and account. Our employees will never ask you for your password.
Disclosure to Third Party Affiliates
You hereby grant us the right to disclose to third parties certain Registration Info about you. The information we obtain through your use of this site, including your Registration Info, is subject to our Privacy Policy, which is specifically incorporated by reference into these Terms of Use.
Disclaimers
YOUR USE OF THIS WEBSITE IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK. THE WEBSITE IS PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" AND "AS AVAILABLE" BASIS. WE RESERVE THE RIGHT TO RESTRICT OR TERMINATE YOUR ACCESS TO THE WEBSITE OR ANY FEATURE OR PART THEREOF AT ANY TIME. THE COMPANY EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND ANY WARRANTIES THAT MATERIAL ON THE WEBSITE IS NONINFRINGING; THAT ACCESS TO THE WEBSITE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE; THAT THE WEBSITE WILL BE SECURE; OR THAT INFORMATION ON THE WEBSITE WILL BE COMPLETE, ACCURATE OR TIMELY. IF YOU DOWNLOAD ANY MATERIAL FROM THIS WEBSITE, YOU DO SO AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION AND RISK. YOU WILL BE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE TO YOUR COMPUTER SYSTEM OR LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS FROM THE DOWNLOAD OF ANY SUCH MATERIAL. NO ADVICE OR INFORMATION, WHETHER ORAL OR WRITTEN, OBTAINED BY YOU FROM US OR THROUGH OR FROM THE WEBSITE SHALL CREATE ANY WARRANTY OF ANY KIND.
Limitation of Liability
TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED UNDER APPLICABLE LAW, YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT NEITHER THE COMPANY NOR ANY OF ITS PARENT, SUBSIDIARY, JOINT VENTURE, PARTNERSHIP OR AFFILIATED COMPANIES OR THIRD-PARTY CONTENT PROVIDERS SHALL BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, PUNITIVE OR ANY OTHER DAMAGES RELATING TO OR RESULTING FROM YOUR USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THIS WEBSITE OR ANY OTHER WEBSITE YOU ACCESS THROUGH A LINK FROM THIS WEBSITE OR FROM ANY ACTIONS WE TAKE OR FAIL TO TAKE AS A RESULT OF ELECTRONIC MAIL MESSAGES YOU SEND US. THESE INCLUDE DAMAGES FOR ERRORS, OMISSIONS, INTERRUPTIONS, DEFECTS, DELAYS, COMPUTER VIRUSES, YOUR LOSS OF PROFITS, LOSS OF DATA, UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO AND ALTERATION OF YOUR TRANSMISSIONS AND DATA, AND OTHER TANGIBLE AND INTANGIBLE LOSSES. THIS LIMITATION APPLIES REGARDLESS OF WHETHER THE DAMAGES ARE CLAIMED UNDER THE TERMS OF A CONTRACT, AS THE RESULT OF NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE, AND EVEN IF WE OR OUR REPRESENTATIVES HAVE BEEN NEGLIGENT OR HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.
Jurisdiction
The laws of the State of California govern these Terms of Use and your use of the Website, and you irrevocably consent to the jurisdiction of the courts located in the State of California for any action to enforce these Terms of Use, the Privacy Policy and the Shipping Policy. We recognize that it is possible for you to obtain access to this Website from any jurisdiction in the world, but we have no practical ability to prevent such access. If any material on this Website, or your use of the Website, is contrary to the laws of the place where you are when you access it, the Website is not intended for you, and we ask you not to use the Website. You are responsible for informing yourself of the laws of your jurisdiction and complying with them.
Changes to These Terms
We reserve the right, at our complete discretion, to change these terms and conditions at any time by posting revised terms on the Website. It is your responsibility to check periodically for any changes we may make to these terms and conditions. Your continued use of this Website following the posting of changes to these terms or other policies means you accept the changes.
Information
MFWC Portal Documentation
Privacy notice
Conditions of Use
My account
Customer info
Addresses
Orders
Copyright © 2020 Miller Family Wine Company Warehouses. All rights reserved.
